https://angasplainswines.com.au/privacy-policy/

Cart
We strive to offer you the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide you an interactive and personalised experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, email address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will never rent, trade or sell, your email address to anyone for any reason whatsoever. Period!
We know that your privacy and personal information is important to you, so that means your privacy is important to us as well. That’s why we have created this policy for your protection and security. Please read it carefully.
We only ask for personal information that we require.
We’ll tell you what information we have recorded about you.
If you would like any personal information about you changed or deleted, just ask.
We do not rent, trade or sell your personal information to anyone.
Who we are
This website is operated by Angas Plains Wines Pty Ltd. Our postal address is PO Box 283, Strathalbyn, SA 5255, Australia. You can reach us via e-mail at: info@angasplainswines.com.au or by telephone at: +61 8 8537 3353
We are an established business with physical premises and our contact details are shown on this website. Only our authorised personnel have access to your data.
How we gather information about visitors to our websites
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you choose to participate and the services provided. You may provide information when you subscribe for our email newsletter, join our mailing list or join PJ’s Wine Connection.
We can only identify you personally if you give us this information voluntarily.
Like most websites, our web servers automatically record some general information about your visit, but do not recognise or record any Personally Identifiable Information about you. The information we record and use for statistical purposes is:
Your server address
The date and time
The pages accessed and documents downloaded
The previous site visited
The type of browser used
Cookies and Session Tracking
Whenever you visit a website anywhere, your browser sends information identifying basic information about the nature of your operating system and the browser you are using. We use cookies and session variables to track the popularity of each page on our site and to understand the overall direction of traffic. We do not analyse or record your individual choices. By understanding the general viewing trends of our visitors, we can design our web pages to make your viewing experience simpler and more user-friendly. Learning how you found us helps us understand what you were looking for on the internet and assists us in tailoring our site for your best viewing experience.
If you visit this website using one of our affiliates links, we use a cookie to keep track of your visit, so we can correctly pay the affiliate a commission if you make a purchase.
Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or it may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our website.
As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do, you may be unable to access certain sections of our website or you may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customise our websites features according to your preferences.
Your email address
We do not know your email address unless you give it to us. We only record your email address if you send us a message, either directly or by registering it on our site. We use it internally within our organisation, and do not sell or rent it to other parties.
When you register with us as a customer, we ask for your email address and information about you. The Personally Identifiable Information you supply is never, ever publicly displayed on our website.
From time to time we email our customers with news, information and offers relating to our own products and services or those of selected partners. These mailings are always conducted by ourselves and never directly by a third party to ensure the security of your information.
How we use this information
This information also allows us to let you know about special offers and new products.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Angas Plains Wines Pty Ltd may be used (but not limited to) for site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of contests, and other communications with you.
Who has access to your information?
Your Personally Identifiable Information is used internally and by people or organisations who need to know it as part of working with us in our normal business activities (e.g. sub-contractors, technical support).
We may need to supply your Personally Identifiable Information to other parties who work with us to provide a product or service to you.
We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in response to a court order, or at times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note that we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
Angas Plains Wines Pty Ltd reserves the right to change this policy at any time. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Corrections
If you would like any personal information about you changed or deleted, just send an email to info@angasplainswines.com.au. and will make the necessary changes as soon as possible. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us at the above address or phone number.
Links to other sites
Where this site contains links to other sites, we do not accept responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.
We encourage other suitable websites to include a link back to this site provided you DO NOT use any trademarks or copyright information without permission.
If you would like to arrange a link, please contact info@angasplainswines.com.au
Security
While we make every effort to keep your information private and away from hackers, it is not possible for us to guarantee your privacy. Please weigh up the risk that your details will be misused by hackers with the benefit of receiving the great information that this site has to offer.
Liability Disclaimer
We will use all reasonable endeavours to protect and keep your personal information confidential. If any of your personal information is accessed by a third party, whether through our negligence or otherwise, to the extent permitted by law, we disclaim any and all liability to any person or organisation for loss, damage or costs.
Governing Law
This policy and the use of this website is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of South Australia, Australia.
If a dispute arises under this policy, which cannot be resolved by negotiation in a reasonable time, the dispute will be submitted for arbitration in accordance with the rules of the Institute of Arbitrators, Australia in the following location: Adelaide, Australia. Each party shall be responsible for its own costs and fees other than legal fees associated with mediation.
This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
More Information
If you would like to know more about online privacy, visit The Australian Privacy Commissioner’s website.
